Jonatan Schultz

Date of birth: 28/09/1996 Nationality: Swedish Address: Jönköping, Sweden

Phone number: +46768378327

Email address: jonatan_schultz@hotmail.com





Profile

I am a system developer with big passion for technology. I have a continuous desire to learn new methods of working, and new ways of thinking. I am a passionate leader and strive to bring to the best out of my colleagues.

- 1 Year experience in dotnet.
- 1 Year experience in QA

Two years of experience with React, TypeScript, NextJs. 1 Year experience Project coordinator & Team Lead system development

Work Experience

₩ 09/2018 - 2020 O BORÅS, SWEDEN

Deviation Handler Speed Competence AB

- Manage the WorkFlow Management System
- · Keep track of deviations
- Use system SAP to handle orders and warehouse management.

 ➡ 11/2020 - 03/2022
 ♦ SVENLJUNGA, SWEDEN

System developer Blåkläder AB

Full-Stack development using C#, TypeScript, NodeJs, React, NextJs, Azure services and more. Quality Assurance & Testing

📛 03/2022 - PRESENT 🥎 SVENLJUNGA, SWEDEN

System Developer & Team Lead Blåkläder AB

- Coordinate project & resource planning
- · Analyze product requirements
- Write code to run and maintain software
- Quality Assurance
- Manage Release & Deployments

Education

📛 01/2018 - 07/2018 🕥 SHANGHAI, CHINA Mandarin | B2 Level **LTL Mandarin School**

➡ 09/2019 - 06/2021 () BORÅS, SWEDEN Systemutveckling .NET Borås Yrkeshögskola

Education

.NET Development, Web development, Databases, Application development, Project methodology, Full-Stack

Skills

(i) LANGUAGES

Swedish **Native** English Full Mandarin Limited Limited Spanish

(i) PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

C# **TypeScript** CSS HTMI SQL XAML

(i) TOOLS AND FRAMEWORKS

Azure REST GIT Agile React Docker NodeJS

Publications

jonatanschultz.com

jonatanschultz.com

Social Media





@jonatan-schultz

@exemplarisk